Woodward, S.C. mss. 1767-1961 LMC 2207
Lilly Library
- IV. Photographs. (Box 2)
  - Nordmo-Loevberg, Aase - Walsh, Blanche (Box 5)
    Talma, Francois Joseph
    Talmadge, Norma
    Tamberlik, Enrico
    Tandy, Jessica
    Taylor, George F.
    Taylor, Laurette
    Taylor, Mary
    Taylor, Nellie
    Tebaldi, Renata
    Tellegen, Lou
    Tempest, Dame Marie Susan
    Templeton, Fay
    Terris, Norma
    Terriss, Ellaline
    Terriss, William
    Terry, Dame Alice Ellen
    Terry, Daniel
    Terry, Fred
    Terry, Marion
    Tetrazzini, Luisa
    Tetzel, Joan
    Thatcher, George
    Thaw, Evelyn Nesbit
    Thebom, Blanche
    Thomas, Dorothy
    Thompson, Jessie
    Thompson, Lydia
    Thorberg, Vin
    Thorndike, Dame Sybil
    Thornton, Maudie
    Three musketeers of the brush
    Tibbett, Lawrence
    Tierney, Gene
    Tietjens, Therese Johanne Alexandra
    Titheradge, Madge
    Tmai, Kunie
    Todd, Ann
    Toole, John Lawrence
    Toumanova, Tamara
    Trailline, Helene
    Tree, Lady Helen Maude (Holt) (Lady Herbert Beerbohm Tree)
    Tree, Sir Herbert Beerbohm
    Tresmond, Ivy
    Trevelyan, Hilda
    Tribble, Etta
    Troijus, Miliza
    Tucci, Gabriella
    Tucker, Richard
    Turner, Claramae
    Turner, Clifford
    Tyler, Dallas
    Tyler, Royall
    Ufer, Gretchen
    Ulrich, Lenore
    Uppman, Theodor
    Ure, Mary
    Urquhart, Isabelle
    Ustinov, Peter Alexander
    Vanbrugh, Dame Irene
    Vanbrugh, Violet
    Vandenhoff, George C.
    Vandenhoff, Mrs. Mary (McKeath) (Mrs. George C. Vandenhoff)
    Van der Vlis, Diana
    Van Dresser, Marcia
    Vanni, Helen
    Varesi, Gilda
    Varnay, Astrid
    Venne, Lottie
    Verdon, Gwen
    Vernon, Joseph
    Victor Emmanuel II, king of Italy
    Von Bulow, Hans
    Von Stosch, Leonora
    Wall, Joan
    Wallace, Yolanda
    Wallack, James William
    Wallack, John Lester
    Waller, Mrs. Florence (Mrs. Lewis Waller)
    Waller, Lewis
    Wallis, Bertram
    Walsh, Blanche
  - Warburton, Charles M. - Unidentified (Box 6)
    Warburton, Charles M.
    Ward, Evelyn
    Ward, Sarah
    Warde, Frederick Barkham
    Warner, Charles John
    Warner, Mrs. Mary Amelia (Huddart) (Mrs. Robert William Warner)
    Warren, Leonard
    Warren, William
    Wassu, Hinda
    Waters, Ethel
    Weathersby, Eliza
    Webster, Margaret
    Wehlen, Emmy
    Welchman, Harry
    Welles, Vicki
    West, Mae
    Wewitzer, Ralph
    Wheatley, William
    Whiffen, Thomas
    Whitty, Dame May
    Wickmire, Nancy
    Wilcox, Mrs. Ella (Wheeler) (Mrs. Robert Wilcox)
    Wilde, Patricia
    Willard, Catherine
    Willard, Edward Smith
    Williams, _____
    Williams, Emlyn
    Williams, Esther
    Williams, Hope
    Willson, Meredith
    Wilson, Francis
    Wilson, Julia
    Wilson, Lois
    Wilson, Marie
    Windsor, Claire
    Wingfield, Conway
    Winstanley, Eliza
    Winter, William
    Winters, Shelley
    Withers, Googie
    Wood, Helen
    Wood, John
    Wood, Leonard
    Wood, Peggy
    Woodward, Henry
    Woodward, Sidney C.
    Worth, Irene
    Worthing, Frank
    Wright, Haidee
    Wright, Huntley
    Wyman, Jane
    Wynter, Dana
    Yates, Edmund
    Yates, Frederick Henry
    Yates, Mary Ann (Graham) (Mrs. Richard Yates)
    Yerence, Ida
    Young, Mrs. _____ (Biggs)
    Young, Charles Mayne
    Young, Clara Kimball
    Younge, A.
    Ysaye, Eugene
    Zorina, Vera
    Unidentified Pictures
  - Oversize Photos (Ovflat 18)
    Duncan, Rosetta
    Eddinger, Wallace
    Greenwood, Charlotte
    Hackett, James Keteltas
    Jeritza, Maria
    Keane, Doris
    Latham, Cynthia
    Lytton, Edward George Earle Lytton Bulwer-Lytton, baron
    Sonderson, Lora
    Smith, William
- V. Folders. (Box 6)
  All folders contain no contents, but feature handwritten notes and annotations in reference to each identified individual.
  - A-Z (Box 6)
    Abbington, Mrs. Francis
    Anson, G.
    Bayly, Thomas Haynes
    Beazley, Samuel
    Bennett, William
    Berkeley, Henry
    Blanchard, Laman
    Booth, Agnes
    Booth, Jr., Junius Brutus
    Bothwick, Peter
    Buckingham, Mrs. C.
    Burton, William E.
    Caulfield, Emily - John Caulfield
    Clarke, Mary Anne
    Davison, Maria
    De Camp, Vincent
    Dejazet, Virginia
    Delane, William
    De Veaux, Emily
    Dickons, Mrs. Peter
    Donne, William B.
    Farren, Mrs. Mary Anne
    Farren, William
    Fiddes, Harriet
    Gillman, William
    Grimaldi, Joey
    Hearn, James A.
    Hodder, George
    Honey, Mrs. Laura
    Howard, George
    Hughes, Henry
    Jones, George
    Loaden, William
    Matthews, C.J.
    Murray, Leigh
    Nugent, M.
    Paget, F.M.
    Pelby, William
    Ringold, Kate
    Robertson, Peter
    Robinson, Emma
    Roselle, Amy
    Selby, Charles
    Shewill, L.R.
    Shuter, Gilbert
    Simpson, Edmund
    Sinclaire, Catherine (ne: Forrest)
    Smythson, _____
    Sparks, Mrs.
    Taylor, Wilbraham
    Thorne, Frederick
    Van Amburgh, Isaac
    Vanderhoff, John M.
    Vanderhoff, Mary
    Weston, M.A.
    Wheatcroft, Nelson
    Williams, Emma